Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Park
  - Subseries D: Looking West
    - Looking West, 1940s and 1950s, 1940-1959 (Box 212, Folder 11)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West, 1953; wsp_lw_5_11_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West - Hayden Hall, 1947; wsp_lw_5_11_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West - Hayden Hall, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_lw_5_11_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 6)
      - Washington Square West, 1953; wsp_lw_5_11_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_lw_5_11_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 8)
    - Looking West, 1960s, 1960-1969 (Box 212, Folder 12)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 1)
      - Corner of Washington Place and Washington Square West, Looking West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 2)
      - Washington Square West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 3)
      - Washington Square South, Looking West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 4)
      - Fountain, Washington Square Park, 1960; wsp_lw_5_12_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square Arch, 1968; wsp_lw_5_12_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 6)
      - Washington Square South and Washington Square South, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, 1961; wsp_lw_5_12_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 8)
      - Drawing, Washington Square Park, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_09; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 9)
      - Drawing, Washington Square Park, 1973; wsp_lw_5_12_10; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 10)
      - Truck, Washington Square West, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_11; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (polaroid) (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 11)
      - Washington Square West, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_12; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (polaroid) (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 12)
      - Washington Square South, Looking West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Park, 1924; wsp_ls_6_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Washington Square South, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_ls_6_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 4)
        stereoscopic photographs.
    - Looking West, Undated (Box 212, Folder 13)
      - Station Wagon Parked on Washington Square South, undated; wsp_lw_5_13_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Subseries E: Looking South
    - Looking South, 1800s (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Mt. Washington Collegiate Institute, Washington Square, 1858; wsp_ls_6_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 1, Item 1)
        Engraving.
    - Looking South, 1900-1909 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Arch and Horse-Drawn Carriages, 1900; wsp_ls_6_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Corner of Washington Square South and Thomson Street, 1905; wsp_ls_6_2_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Looking South, 1920-1929 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square South, 1925; wsp_ls_6_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square, Looking South, 1924; wsp_ls_6_3_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking South, 1924; wsp_ls_6_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Outdoor Art Show, Washington Square South, circa 1920-1929; wsp_ls_6_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches, copy print of stereograph (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1920-1929; wsp_ls_6_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 3 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Washington Square South, 1925; wsp_ls_6_3_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Looking South, 1930-1939 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square South, Aerial View, circa 1930-1939; wsp_ls_6_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1935; wsp_ls_6_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Snow in Washington Square Park and Washington Square South, Aerial View, 1937; wsp_ls_6_4_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Judson Building, Washington Square South, circa 1930; wsp_ls_6_4_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Looking South, 1940-1949 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square South and Sullivan Street, 1945; wsp_ls_6_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Washington Square South, undated; wsp_ls_6_5_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Washington Square South and Wooster Street, 1925; wsp_ls_6_5_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - 100 Washington Square East, Looking South From Washington Square North, 1949; wsp_ls_6_5_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Looking South, 1950-1959 (Box 213, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square South, Site of Vanderbilt Hall, circa 1950-1959; wsp_ls_6_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Shimkin Hall, Washington Square Southeast, 1955; wsp_ls_6_6_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1953; wsp_ls_6_6_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Southeast, after Demolition, 1958; wsp_ls_6_6_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Southeast, Demolition, 1957; wsp_ls_6_6_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Southeast, Demolition, 1957; wsp_ls_6_6_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking South, circa 1950-1959; wsp_ls_6_6_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 7)
    - Looking South, 1960-1969 (Box 213, Folder 7)
      - Washington Square Arch, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1966; wsp_ls_6_7_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - New York University Buildings, Washington Square Area, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_ls_6_7_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - Washington Square South and Washington Square West, 1962; wsp_ls_6_7_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - 51 Washington Square South, 1969; wsp_ls_6_7_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - 51 Washington Square South and Judson Building, 1964; wsp_ls_6_7_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking South from 5th Avenue, 1966; wsp_ls_6_7_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_ls_6_7_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - Judson Building, Washington Square South, circa 1960-1969; wsp_ls_6_7_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - New York University Buildings, Washington Square Park, wsp_ls_6_7_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, undated; wsp_ls_6_7_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Arch, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1966; wsp_ls_6_7_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 7, Item 11)
    - Looking South, 1970-1979 (Box 213, Folder 8)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1978; wsp_ls_6_8_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Washington Square South at Night, Aerial View, 1973; wsp_ls_6_8_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Looking South, Undated (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Subseries F: Looking North
    - Looking North, 1870-1909 (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Men and Carriages on Washington Square West, Looking North, 1894; wsp_ln_7_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1870; wsp_ln_7_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, undated; wsp_ln_7_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1870; wsp_ln_7_1_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, circa 1890; wsp_ln_7_1_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1900-1910; wsp_ln_7_1_06; black-and-white copyprint (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Arch, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1907; wsp_ln_7_1_07; sepia copyprint (photograph), 8 x 10 inches
    - Looking North, 1910-1919 (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Women's Labor March, Washington Square Park, 1912; wsp_ln_7_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 214, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - 5th Avenue Coach Company Stop, Washington Square, 1915; wsp_ln_7_2_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Looking North, 1920-1929 (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, 1926; wsp_ln_7_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1921; wsp_ln_7_3_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square East, Looking North, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_ln_7_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking Northeast, 1921; wsp_ln_7_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 214, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Washington Square North, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_ln_7_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Looking North, 1930-1939 (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking East, 1939; wsp_ln_7_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Federal Theatre Project Caravan, Washington Square Park, circa 1930 - 1938; wsp_ln_7_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park and Fountain, circa 1930 - 1939; wsp_ln_7_4_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 9 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Washington Square North and 5th Avenue, circa 1930 - 1939; wsp_ln_7_4_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking Northwest, 1938; wsp_ln_7_4_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - The Row, Washington Square Park, 1939; wsp_ln_7_4_06; hand-painted black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Looking North, 1940-1949 (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North From Commerce Building, 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Washington Square North, Looking Northwest, 1945; wsp_ln_7_5_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Washington Square North, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking North, 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - North Side of Washington Square North looking East from Fifth Avenue, 1948; wsp_ln_7_5_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 6)
      - Bus and Washington Square Arch, Looking North, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 7)
      - Waverly Place at Washington Square North, Looking West, 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 8)
      - South Side of Waverly Place, Looking West from Washington Square North, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 9)
      - Looking North along Washington Park North, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 10)
      - Greene Street and West 3rd Street, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 11)
      - The Row, Washington Square North, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 12)
      - The Row, Washington Square North, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_ln_7_5_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 5, Item 13)
    - Looking North, 1950-1959 (Box 214, Folder 6)
      - The Row, Washington Square North, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_ln_7_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_ln_7_6_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Washington Square East, Looking North, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_ln_7_6_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - The Row, Washington Square North, 1952; wsp_ln_7_6_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 6, Item 4)
    - Looking North, 1960-1969 (Box 214, Folder 7)
      - The Row, Washington Square North, 1965; wsp_ln_7_7_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 2 x 3 inches (Box 214, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - Fountain, Washington Square Park, 1962; wsp_ln_7_7_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - People Walking, Washington Square Park, 1966; wsp_ln_7_7_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square North, Looking North, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_ln_7_7_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - Bust of Sylvette, undated; wsp_ln_7_7_05; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_ln_7_7_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 214, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - Washington Square North, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_ln_7_7_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square Arch, Looking North, 1965; wsp_ln_7_7_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 214, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square Arch, Looking North, 1961; wsp_ln_7_7_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 7, Item 9)
    - Looking North, 1970-1979 (Box 214, Folder 8)
      - The Row, Washington Square North, circa 1970 - 1971; wsp_ln_7_8_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 214, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking North, 1977; wsp_ln_7_8_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1970 - 1979; wsp_ln_7_8_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 214, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - Looking North, Undated (Box 214, Folder 9)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square Arch, Looking North, undated; wsp_ln_7_9_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 9, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Arch, looking northwest from top of building, undated; wsp_ln_7_9_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 x 9 inches (Box 214, Folder 9, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_ln_7_9_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 214, Folder 9, Item 3)
      - Curb, Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_ln_7_9_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 214, Folder 9, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Snowy Day, undated; wsp_ln_7_9_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 9, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_ln_7_9_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 214, Folder 9, Item 6)
    - Looking North, detail, undated (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Subseries C: Looking East
      - Looking East, 1850s-1860s, 1850-1860 (Box 210, Folder 4)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1858; wsp_le_4_4_01; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 4, Item 1)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1891; wsp_le_4_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7½ inches (Box 210, Folder 4, Item 2)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, ca 1860-1869; wsp_le_4_4_03; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Looking East, 1880s-1890s, 1880-1890 (Box 210, Folder 5)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1880-1890; wsp_le_4_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Looking East, 1900-1909 (Box 210, Folder 6)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1890-1899; wsp_le_4_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 6, Item 1)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1905; wsp_le_4_6_02 (Box 210, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Looking East, 1910-1919 (Box 210, Folder 7)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1915; wsp_le_4_7_01 (Box 210, Folder 7, Item 1)
          General note
          black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches
      - Looking East, 1920-1929 (Box 210, Folder 8)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1920-1929; wsp_le_4_8_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 1)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 2)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 3)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1920-1929; wsp_le_4_8_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 4)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1921; wsp_le_4_8_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 5)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 6)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 8 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 7)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1925; wsp_le_4_8_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 8)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 9 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 9)
        - Washington Square Area, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 10)
        - Washington Square Area, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 11)
        - Washington Square Area, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 12)
        - Washington Square Park, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7½ inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 13)
        - Washington Square Park, wsp_le_4_8_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 14)
        - Main Building, Washington Square Park, 1921; wsp_le_4_8_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 15)
        - Main Building, Washington Square Park, 1921; wsp_le_4_8_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 16)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_le_4_8_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 17)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 18)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking Northeast, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 19)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 20)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 21)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 22)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 23)
        - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_le_4_8_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 24)
      - Looking East, 1930-1939 (Box 212, Folder 1)